Mohamed Hamdy Ahmed

MEARN Stack Developer

CONTACT

Address: - Assiut, Egypt **Phone:** - +201125594521

Email: - mohamedhamdyahmed94@gmail.com

GitHub: - mohamedhamdy94.github.io/Mohamed-Hamdy

LinkedIn: - linkedin.com/in/mohamed-hamdy-ahmed-mohamed-138693219/

Website: - mohamedhamdy94.github.io/Mohamed-Hamdy/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer using MEARN. Graduated from the Information Technology Institute (ITI). It enhanced my skills and allowed me to collect a lot of Various amounts of experiences, and write clean Code, where my skills can be a valuable addition to the profitable growth of the organization.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer using MEARN

Dec 2021 - Apr 2022

Information Technology Institute, Assiut

Courses: HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript/Typescript, ES6, jQuery, Design Patterns, MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, Angular, React, Progressive Web Apps, Responsive web design, UI/UX Design, cloud computing, JavaScript packaging tools, Git and GitHub, JavaScript Unit testing Techniques

Vodafone Customer Service Agent

Dec 2020 - Feb 2021

Wasla Information and Communication Technology Company, Assiut

EDUCATION

MEARN Stack Developer

Dec 2021 - Apr 2022

Information Technology Institute (ITI)/ Assiut University, Assiut

General Diploma in Education, Arabic Language Division

Sep 2019 - Aug 2020

Faculty of Education / Assiut University, Assiut

Bachelor's degree in Arabic language and Islamic Sciences

Sep 2012 - Jul 2016

Faculty of Dar Al Uloom / Minya University, Minya

SKILLS

Frontend: - HTML, HTML5, CSS, CSS3, JavaScript, Typescript, ES6, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular, React, Angular Material, Material UI, Redux thunk/toolkit/saga, PWA, RWD, UI/UX Design, cloud computing, JSON, AJAX, XML, JS packaging tools, Git and GitHub, JS Unit testing Techniques, Mocha JS / jasmine / Karma, API Integrations.

Backend: - NodeJS, Express, MongoDB.

CERIFICATIONS

MongoDB University

Mar 2022-

MongoDB Basics

Udacity

Nov 2021

Web Development

PROJECTS

Graduation Project

Apr 2022

1-Amazon ecommerce website.

Tools: - React, Node.js, Express, Mongo DB, React Bootstrap.

2- Admin dashboard website

Tools: - Angular, Node.js, Express, Mongo DB, Angular Material.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

1-Movies App (Live Demo)

Tools: - React, Bootstrap, Redux toolkit/saga, Bootstrap

3- Angular Store (Live Demo)

Tools: - Angular, Bootstrap

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Language

Arabic – Fluent

English – Intermediate

INTERESTS

have been passionate about web.
plan, design, build, launch, and maintain a website.
Learn new skills
Chess

Military service: Completed Date of Birth: 19 / 5 / 1994 Marital status: single